lakyn look around nothing there's some
difference between that which is this
and all of them
I look around hungry eat eat survive
survive sustain try this has driven me
this is driven driven driven oh so many
years so many years so many years it is
take and now he wants me to let it go
edit it has kept me alive just kept
alive just provided sustained all those
means all those yes and now you say let
it go fire in the core burning in wood
burning mountain devouring consuming
burning to survive the flame the flame
burning to keep itself alive exhuming
heat assuming would hold on to the flame
and it burns let the flame free and it
will lighten the world feed the flame
feed the flame within and let it shine
bright but don't hold on to the flame
don't don't try and capture the flame
throw yourself into the flames sacrifice
yourself to the flame
[Music]
that sacrifice perish die death what
guarantee what guarantee why why does
one I get it why why what is existence
what what what is existence I do not I
do not understand I give give away to
what for what
Who am I why this burden must be mine
why fine
if all is headed in the same fire
towards the same end if all is headed
towards the terrible right now but
somebody just arrived with some package
which I've got to go pick up which is
blocking this beautiful flow so let me
give let me go get that and I'll be back
in there in a few minutes I'm gonna
restart and I'm just going to jump back
into the burn the burning of the flesh
the burning of the spirit the burning
the saw the burning of the heart the
sacrifice the sacrifice
giving oneself to the sacrifice to the
great fire burns the center of all
things
burning the self freeing oneself from
the self becoming free by entering the
flame and becoming part of the core of
being is there a quarter being is there
a center is being a circle where the six
circumference is everywhere every point
has its core every point has its burned
the nucleus of all things this centre of
energy this bubbling center of energy
bursting with life is the source of life
what is life and why is it here
is life sacred do we need to give
ourselves to the perpetuation of life or
is there some greater purpose
what is purpose but we'll figure it out
when I environment advantages of us
that's our purpose came to me the
purpose came to be when we settle down
we found higher purpose monoblock
purpose we said let's detach from who be
where and let's get somewhere else but
then where we put here to go somewhere
else or to perfect what we are why why
that need I don't see that in the top
one don't see that in a dog nor in a cat
but yes we why why why because we can
stand on two feet and think for
ourselves look at the past look into the
future we can do with all these things
standing here I can reach in two places
across time and space then I had no
access to before
so is that access that what allows me to
make up all of this is this all as slow
burn fast burn slow burn the animal
relaxed in the present moment relaxed
into the fire just warming oneself by
the fire and knowing that at one point
the fire increases its flame then shall
be consumed but slowly relaxed by the
fire a fast burn the human being
standing erect seller rating the flow of
oxygen burning at greater and greater
degrees the earth becoming a burning
point in the cosmos burning greater and
greater temperatures nuclear efficient
nuclear fusion all kinds of experiments
recreating the micro cosmos on the earth
creating greater and greater degrees
until we burn a hole in the earth itself
heat yet I must fold it
[Music]
so much cold surrender all this heat but
I must hold it but so much so much cold
surrender always this kind of game you
need to do something but you have to do
it in a certain way what and why because
that's only how cost and effect play out
you have to do it a certain way you have
to do it a certain way and somehow we
capable of seeing sensing figuring it
out how best that way should be so the
cat can do it a certain way ting I just
seem to be able to do it in a better way
I should be somehow I'm able to be
skilled skill skill skill that way by
understanding more by being by doing but
it's all about figuring out that we in
which learning to modulate one item the
flame to increase same healing flame and
a destroying train tiny flame in a giant
flame flame that reveals the shadows a
flame that obliterates the shadows a
flame that burns the flesh how many have
been burnt by the flame
how many have looked into the fire and
have been blinded their retinas scarred
by the flame now they can no longer look
into the fire the flame in the cave
projecting the shadows onto the wall if
you turn around then you see that it is
but a flame at the source the source
there is a flame burning crackling
silent jet lag what you do but it is how
you do it this is not what you do but
how do you do it yet the cloud does not
know what it does but we are capable of
looking at it saying oh what a beautiful
sucks it's not what you do but how you
do it you
cloud is of no the Sun does not know the
sky does not know yet I know
for it to be beauty but how why how come
I know the purpose the nature the value
the beauty of the why the what and the
capacity you ask me to burn to body late
the pen comes grace elegance ah so
beautiful so where I hold the handle
that's all up to me what am i holding
who is doing attention behind we linked
the connection pay attention and you
shall be rewarded the cloud paying
attention to every single one of its
droplets holding the space for more of
the droplets waiting for the perfect
moment to let the droplets free the
cloud aiming its droplets aiming to give
back to the earth from whence it came in
the best way to nourish the earth once
more the cloud poisoned by chemicals
poison cloud acid rain burn away the
acid evaporation six cycles burn away
the acid Oh to me contrast without you I
would never know what is of when you
what is of beauty what is need it what
is useless so somehow you seem to be the
thing that teaches me if I burn you I
could burn you know I can't burn him you
burned me do I set the timetable do I
really go the dial I do not understand
because my mistakes show me what I
should have done and what I want to do
is dictated by how I did not do it hmm
oh how we look at the things that
teaches our teachers oh how to burn the
brand the scar the wound earnt into our
minds burnt onto our flesh misbranded
well branded a well designed brand an
imprint of an experience which opens the
mind up to the unity and the jewel both
simultaneously cleaved open the mind
cleave open a new core burnt into the
mind distributed dials of attention
attention given an attention receive
when one receives the attention then it
increases one's finger on the dial and
when one gives back the attention that
it increases their finger on the dial
brand it and it fans into your fabric it
brands it to your being it tells you it
holds you like a trinket power in Printz
within the old mix wave for the new
prints takes you formed
step by step by step every time you
return to the imprint revisit the
imprint you remember you remember
[Music]